wrif.com 2016-10-19

# Privacy Policy - WRIF Rocks Detroit

## Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy was last updated on April 1, 2015 and is effective immediately.  It applies to all Greater Media radio stations and related properties, including WRIF.

This Privacy Policy has been updated as of April 2015 to provide information about the inclusion of certain audience measurement products developed by The Nielsen Company, which may be deployed within the Sites’ streaming music players and within Station mobile applications.

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) covers the collection, use and dissemination of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) by Greater Media, Inc. (“Company”) and/or its subsidiaries which own and operate Station (collectively, “we,” “us,” or “our”), and its websites (“Sites”), Facebook page and other social network platforms, mobile applications, text messaging services, offline activities and promotions, and any service that has an authorized link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, “Services”). Please take a moment to read this Privacy Policy to learn more about our Personal Information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how it is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your Personal Information. By using our Services, you consent to the information practices described in this Privacy Policy.

Any references to Company, Station or we, us, and our, for purposes of this Privacy Policy, also includes the third party entities that provide internal support for our Services, (“Operational Service Providers”), unless stated otherwise.

This Privacy Policy has been incorporated by reference into our [Terms of Use agreement](http://www.wrif.com/termsofuse/) (“TOU”). Any capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy will have the same meaning as defined in our TOU.

Our Services are intended for United States audiences over the age of 13 (in many cases, over the age of 18). All of our Services are governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the U. S. We make no representation that any Service is operated in accordance with the laws or governed by other nations. If you are not a U.S. citizen or do not reside in the U.S., please be aware that by using these Services and/or submitting your Personal Information, you voluntarily consent to our collection, transfer, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information to the U.S. You also agree to waive any claims that may arise under your own national laws. We will reject or delete any Personal Information that we believe in good faith to be inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

  1. **Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with us and want to receive information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, you must send a request to the following address with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). You may contact us in two ways. Send email to [privacyadministrator@greatermediadetroit.com](mailto:privacyadminisrator@greatermediadetroit.com).  **Alternatively, you may contact us at:**

**WRIF** **  
**WRIF.com**  
**Greater Media Detroit**  
**1 Radio Plaza**  
**Detroit, MI 48220**  
**Attn: Your California Privacy Rights**** **  
**c/o Privacy Administrator****

**For requests sent via email, you must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your email. All requests sent via postal mail must be labeled “Your California Privacy Rights” on the envelope or post card and clearly stated on the actual request.**  For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. (Your street address is optional if you wish to receive a response to your request via email. Please include your zip code for our own recordkeeping.) **We will not accept requests via the telephone or by facsimile**. We are not responsible for responding to notices that are not labeled or not sent properly, or do not have complete information.

For all other users of this Site or other Services, if you have other questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact our Privacy Administrator at the following email address: [privacyadministrator@greatermediadetroit.com](mailto:privacyadminisrator@greatermediadetroit.com). **or** :

**WRIF** **  
**WRIF.com**  
**Greater Media Detroit**  
**1 Radio Plaza**  
**Detroit, MI 48220**** **  
**Attn: Privacy Administrator****

  2. **How We Collect Your Information**

The information we learn from users helps us personalize and continually improve your experience with our Services. We collect Personal Information, which is traditionally information that by itself can be used to identify or contact a specific individual person, such as your email address, name, home or work address or wireline and/or mobile telephone number. We will also collect data that can be reasonably linked to a specific consumer, computer or device. For example, we will automatically collect your Internet protocol address (“IP Address”), or a unique device identifiers for mobile devices (“UDID”) when you access our Sites or mobile applications. IP Addresses and UDIDs were traditionally classified as Non-Personal Information because they did not identify a specific individual user. When an IP Address or UDID is associated or linked with other Personal Information, or used to monitor usage, search and transaction history or build a user profile for the purposes of customizing your experience or advertising on our Platforms, such information will be classified as Personal Information to the extent required by applicable law.

Depending on your relationship with us and the Services that you will use, in addition to that more traditional forms of Personal Information, we will also collect your Facebook, Twitter or other social networking user ID and password (and any other Personal and/or Non-Personal Information that you allow Facebook or any other platform to share with us), date of birth, gender, occupation/employer, and purchasing preferences, photos/videos or audio clips of you, facsimile number, and geolocation data that will tell us your specific or general location. We also collect Personal Information offline via contests or other promotions conducted via telephone (such as contests and promotions that encourage you to call in to our radio programs), text and instant messaging, postal mail, or facsimile, and in person at events, concerts, fairs, retail locations, and other remote locations. We may also collect your Personal Information when you join our various loyal-listener, email marketing and other membership-oriented clubs offline, as well as employment applications.

We may combine your online Personal Information with Personal Information collected offline, via your Facebook, Twitter or other social networking platforms, or other third party companies, such as credit bureaus, background check firms, marketing research companies, and Advertisers.

We also collect Non-Personal Information, which is generally information that cannot by itself be used to identify a specific individual person. Non-Personal Information includes information about your computer, browser, mobile device, visits to our Services and other online activities that are used for internal operations, to enhance or customize your experience, and to improve our Services. Personal Information that is de-identified (meaning it becomes anonymous) and combined with other users’ anonymous Personal Information (also called “aggregated” information) is also Non-Personal information because it cannot be used to identify a specific individual. However, Non-Personal Information linked to or associated with Personal Information will also be classified as Personal Information.

We also collect Non-Personal Information, via a software development kit (SDK) developed by The Nielsen Company, about your online listening to the Station stream via our browser player or mobile application. This information is used to supplement other information-gathering techniques used by Nielsen to create and issue Nielsen Audio audience ratings.   You have the right to opt out of this listening measurement by clicking: <http://www.nielsen.com/content/corporate/policy/en/cookie-policy.html>

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose Personal Information through Station public areas such as message boards, blogs, or chat rooms, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Station does not read any of your private online communications.

  3. **How We Use Your Information**

We receive and store any Personal Information you enter during registrations, account creation or any information you voluntarily provide us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain Personal Information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the Personal Information that you provide to us for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing your experience, improving our products and services, and communicating with you to inform you of other products or services available from Station, its affiliates and Advertisers. We may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

We collect Personal and Non-Personal Information to assist us in delivering a superior level of product and service. We collect such information to gain a better understanding of your needs and what types of features, activity or content are most popular with users, and thus provide a better experience for you. Reviewing your information and use of our Services enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services, focus on categories of greatest interest to you, keep you posted on the latest product announcements, updates, special offers, promotions, and events that you might like to hear about.

  4. **Use of Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Technology**

Our Sites and certain other Services will passively collect Personal and Non-Personal Information via cookies, web beacons and other similar technology. This information reveals the frequency with which you visit our Services, the times and dates of your visits, the pages or features and activities you reviewed, and other information, including your IP Address and UDID. We also use navigational data, including log files and click-stream data, to identify information about your web browser and operating system, and the time period in which you visit our Sites or select pages or areas of our Sites. This information is also used to improve our Site's content and is retained anonymously, meaning that it does not identify an individual user. This information is also used to improve our software and services by providing personalized content recommendations, location customization, and/or personalized help and instructions. In addition, we track content accesses and downloads for the purpose of paying royalties and license fees to third party providers, such as record labels, advertisers and other copyright holders and content distributors.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features or activities of our Sites or Services.

  5. **Use of Your Information for Advertising, Marketing & Social Networks**

Advertising support allows us to offer many Services, and features and activities to users such as contests, sweepstakes and special events for free or very little cost. We will also share your Personal Information with our advertisers, sponsors or promotional partners (collectively, “Advertisers”) for ** ** the marketing of events, products or services, but only with your knowledge and consent. When we plan to share your Personal Information with Advertisers, you will receive such notice on the registration area of the website, in the rules of participation for the Service, activity or event, or via a message delivered via radio broadcast or email. Depending on the Service, feature or activity, we will either ask you for your consent first to receive marketing information directly from our Advertisers via the registration process for a particular Service, activity or event, or by participating in the Service, feature or activity, you agree and acknowledge that your Personal Information will be shared with Advertisers for marketing purposes.

Our Advertisers, Facebook and other social networks may collect Personal and Non-Personal Information directly or passively using cookies, web beacons and other technology. This Privacy Policy does not govern the information that Advertisers, Facebook or other social networks may collect. Please be informed that our Advertisers, Facebook and other social networks may not have the same privacy policies or business practices that we do **.** ** ** We encourage you to review their privacy policies to make sure you understand how they use the Personal Information you provide to them. If you do not wish for such a transfer of your Personal Information to take place, you should not register for the applicable Service, feature or activity, or use a Facebook or other social network plug-in or link. We are not responsible for removing your Personal Information from an Advertiser or third party with which you have previously authorized us to share your information. You will need to contact those entities directly.

Here’s a description of the types of advertising that we may serve to you: Contextual, First-Party, and Third-Party Network Advertising. We may use your Personal and Non-Personal Information for advertising-related purposes, such as:

\- Customizing ads based on your geographic region or demographic segment or other Non-Personal Information collected about you;

\- Limiting the number of times you see a particular ad;

\- Showing ads in a particular sequence;

\- Determining when you respond to ads;

\- Reporting aggregated statistics.

We may share aggregated Non-Personal Information publicly and with our partners, such as publishers, Advertisers or connected web sites. For example, we may share Non-Personal Information to show trends about the general use of our Services and any features or activities. Additionally, we may be required to provide specific access and usage information to certain content providers and rights holders as a condition of content licensing and royalties. In such cases, we will provide content usage, access, demographic and other information to the content provider without your Personal Information.

We may disclose relevant information about our users to other contractors (e.g. a customer service contractor or a credit card clearing/processing service) in order for the contractor to provide specific services, and to better serve our customers. Our contractors and Operational Service Providers are bound by strict contractual requirements to keep all Personal Information they process strictly confidential and to use such information solely on behalf of Company or Station and not for the Operational Service Providers’ own marketing or advertising purposes.

Here are additional ways we use your Personal Information:

**Marketing Via Mobile Devices**

**Email**

**Shopping & E-Commerce**

In connection with the sale of goods and/or services or for contest prize fulfillment, we may request Sensitive Personal Information. “Sensitive Personal Information” includes, but is not limited to, any individual’s: (1) social security number; (2) driver’s license number or state identification card number; (3) employee identification number; or (4) credit or debit card number, with or without any required security code, or PIN. Sensitive Personal Information will only be used for verification of your identity, federal or state tax reporting requirements, and/or to implement and complete the specific activity or event it was submitted for. We will not share your Sensitive Personal Information for marketing or promotional purposes, or with other third parties unless such disclosure is required by law. We may also request additional Personal Information such as full name, billing and shipping address, email address and telephone number and any such information that is required to fulfill your order and to communicate with you regarding your order. We may use your Personal Information (but not your credit card or debit card number) to contact you about future products, services and discounts or to provide such information indirectly from our Advertisers, unless you tell us otherwise (i.e. “opt-out”). We will only use your credit card and debit card number to complete the specific transaction you requested. Alternatively, we may use an independent third party Operational Service Provider to conduct the financial transaction in a secure manner; the third party payment process will be accessible via a hyperlink from the Site or other Services and the Operational Service Provider will be solely responsible for all financial transactions and the collection, use, and storage of your Sensitive Personal Information.

  6. **Children’s Privacy Policy**

Although persons of all ages may visit our Site and other Services and participate in activities that do not require the collection of Personal Information, we do not knowingly or intentionally collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13, and in some cases (as specified on the home page of the Site) we discourage participation by anyone under the age of 18. Except for the limited circumstances listed below, we will automatically reject and delete (to the extent technically feasible) the registration or entry of any person we believe in good faith to be underage unless such information meets an exception under the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) or pertains to the programming or operations of Station. Online or offline correspondence from children that pertains to the programming or operations of Station is subject to Federal Communications Commission (“FCC”) regulations that require broadcast licensees to post such correspondence in the applicable Station’s FCC Public Inspection File. We retain the right to block out or edit the postal and email address, text number and/or name of the child. Except to meet FCC regulations, other applicable laws, or other regulatory and legal purposes, we will not knowingly use, distribute or disclose any child's Personal Information to third parties without prior parental consent.

Any false or fraudulent registration or entry from a minor (a person under the age of 18) will be deemed to be ineligible and will disqualify the minor from the receipt of a prize, benefit, or other participation. Unless we are required to retain a minor’s Personal Information for regulatory, tax or other legal purposes, we will promptly remove such information from our database (to the extent technically feasible) if a parent withdraws his or her consent to our use of the minor’s Personal Information.

  7. **When We Disclose Information to Third Parties.**

We do not use your Personal Information for purposes incompatible with those listed above. Your Personal Information will be disclosed to affiliated and unaffiliated third parties only as listed in this Privacy Policy. In addition to completing or fulfilling your transaction, activity or request, we will also disclose your Personal Information if we have received your consent at the time we collect your Personal Information, if you have consented prior to our disclosure, and/or under the following limited circumstances:

  * To Company affiliates for business, operational, promotional and marketing purposes.
  * To Advertisers if you participate in a co-branded, co-sponsored, or jointly presented promotion/contest or service, or to serve personalized or targeted advertising.
  * To our Operational Service Providers, who are prohibited from using your Personal Information for any purpose not authorized by us or required by law.
  * To protect the security of our Services, servers, network systems, and databases.
  * To protect our users, affiliates, Advertisers, and Operational Service Providers against liability and harm.
  * To implement and enforce our TOU or DMCA copyright complaint procedures.
  * To respond to subpoenas, judicial processes, or government requests and investigations.
  * To act in response to an emergency or situation that threatens the life, health or security of an individual, and to assist in the investigation of a violation (or presumed violation) of law, or if we believe in good faith that the law requires or authorizes such disclosure.
  * In connection with any proposed or actual purchase, sale, lease, merger, assignment, re-organization or financing of all or any portion of the Company, our Services, Stations, or any of the business, assets or shares of our parent company(s) and affiliates.

We reserve the right to use, disclose and process any Non-Personal Information collected from you in any manner.

Personalized Content and Advertising Using Third Party Ad Networks

We license and/or utilize technology to serve targeted and non-targeted advertisements on our Services and within our content as that content is served across the Internet. (See Section above titled, “Use of Your Information for Advertising, Marketing & Social Networks” for details.) In addition, we may also use third party ad network providers, including Google, to help present advertisements on the Services, as well as third party analytics vendors to evaluate and provide us with information about the use of our Services and viewing of our content. Some of the ads you see on our Sites and other Services are customized based on automated predictions about your interests, which predictions are generated from your visits over time and across different websites, using tools such as Google Analytics. This information allows us to create content of greater interest to you and can also be used to serve ads based on your past visits to our Sites. Note that you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies, including use by Google, by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page (<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>). Here are links to the opt-out tools of other third party Network Advertising providers on our Services.

<http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

For more information about how targeted Network Advertising works, please visit: <http://www.youradchoices.com/> or <http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising>.

**How to Opt-Out of Targeted Advertising by Network Advertising Services**

You may opt-out of third party targeted advertising served by Network Advertising service providers in two ways: 1) By directly notifying a Network Advertising service provider via its opt-out tools (Please see above) or 2) using your browser’s Do Not Track (DNT) settings to indicate that you do not wish to receive targeted advertising based on your overall internet usage. For more information about DNT and how it works, please visit the Future of Privacy Forum’s website: <http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>.

We will make a good faith reasonable effort to honor your DNT browser settings for opting out of receiving targeted third party advertising based on your overall Internet usage. Please note that various browsers frequently update technology or change their settings and business practices without advance notice, and we may not have the latest information on how to honor your preferences. If you exercise either opt-out option – the cookie opt-out or the browser opt-out – you will continue to receive advertising, but such advertising may not relate to your specific interests, previous purchases or search history.

However, you cannot opt-out of our contextual or first party advertising, which is based on your usage of only our Services and may be combined with your usage of our social media sites. We will continue to serve you contextual and first party advertising. We will also continue to monitor your usage and search or transaction history to provide us with analytics on how well our Services, advertisements and features and activities are functioning and used. We will also share this information in an aggregated form (meaning that no one individual person can be identified) to our Advertisers or potential Advertisers.

  8. **Additional Opt-in or Opt-out Choices for Use of Your Personal Information**

Depending on the Service, feature or activity, you will have the option to either opt-in or opt-out of our use of your Personal Information for marketing or promotional message sent by us for our own events, features or activities. For example, we may send a marketing email message and you use the designated method in the email, as we cannot guarantee that other methods of notification will be effective or timely. You may also opt-out of text message promotions or subscriptions by following the instructions in the text message.

  9. **Links to Third Party Websites and Third Party Content.**

This Privacy Policy does not cover third party advertising or third party content that may be present on our Sites or other Services. We may provide banner and general advertising from third parties, in addition to other content provided by our Advertisers or Operational Service Providers. Users may from time to time purchase goods or services offered through, or otherwise participate in or send messages concerning, such advertising, promotions or third party goods, services, or content offered through the Site or other Services. Such correspondence, transactions and agreements are solely between the user and the Advertiser or the third party provider and do not involve us.

Our Services often provides links to third party websites that could be of interest to our users, including the websites of our Advertisers. We do not own or control these websites and therefore, we are not responsible for the content, business practices, or operations of such websites. Third party websites linked on this Site or other Services may have different privacy policies and business practices than we do and you are encouraged to read their privacy policy first. The presence of a link to a third party website does not constitute or imply our endorsement, recommendation, or sponsorship of the third party content, goods, or services available through, or contained on, the site. By use of this Site and other Services, you have agreed that you will use the hyperlinks to third party sites at your own risk. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of third party owned or operated websites you choose to link to from our Services so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your Personal and Non-Personal Information.

  10. **Security of your Personal Information**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to secure your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide in a controlled, secure environment. When Sensitive Personal Information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to us, it is protected through the use of industry-standard secured Internet connection, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) or S-HTTP protocols. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. By transmitting Personal Information over the Internet, you are accepting any risks associated with doing so. In addition, you are responsible for taking appropriate measures to protect and secure all passwords, log-on or membership identification information and account information.

  11. **Changes, Corrections, or Deletions to Your Personal Information**

You may change or correct any of your Personal Information collected online through the Site or other Services via your account setting on our Site-related Services, or via a written request to [privacyadministrator@greatermediadetroit.com](mailto:privacyadminisrator@greatermediadetroit.com) . You will need to follow the instructions on the Site or other Services. Please be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases without some residual data due to technical limitations of our systems, or retention and/or record keeping requirements under federal and state law. For example, although you may opt-out of any email marketing subscription program, loyal listener club or other membership clubs, our system does not delete your email address from our database. We can, however, deactivate your email address so that you do not receive any further marketing messages. You may delete any Personal Information collected via our non-contest text message promotions but we are required to retain contest entries – regardless of the entry method – for a period of years due to regulatory requirements. If you wish to delete Personal Information collected offline, please contact our Privacy Administrator.

Please be aware that we do not control certain privacy settings and preferences maintained by social media partners like Facebook and Twitter. If you wish to make changes to those settings and preferences, you may do so by visiting the settings page of the appropriate social media site.

  12. **Changes to this Policy**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the law, technology or our business practices. Station encourages you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are using or protecting your information. We will post a notice when we make material changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Services following the posting of any changes to this Policy constitutes acceptance of those changes.

  13. **Contact Information**

We welcome your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that we have not adhered to this Policy, please contact us at [privacyadministrator@greatermediadetroit.com](mailto:privacyadminisrator@greatermediadetroit.com) or the postal address listed below. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

**ADDENDUM #1: IP ADDRESSES**  
An IP Address and UDID are a series of numbers that are automatically assigned to your computer or device and used by us to identify your computer or device. We will use this information to administer our Services, help identify and diagnose problems with our servers and/or operating systems, analyze trends, track users’ webpage movements to help improve our Services, help identify you and your shopping preferences, and gather broad demographic information for aggregating with other users to measure our performance. An IP Address and UDID can also be used to deliver targeted and personalized advertising based on your IP Address' geographic location, or your usage, transaction or search history.

**ADDENDUM #2: COOKIES** **  
** Our Sites use small text files called "cookies" that are sent to the hard drive of your computer to store bits of information related to your use of our Site. Cookies can store a variety of information, including IP Addresses, navigational data, server information, data transfer times, user preferences, shopping cart information and passwords needed to access our Site. We may use cookies to serve customized advertising or content to you based on your submitted zip code, age, gender, or other demographics. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Station pages, or register with the Site or particular features, activities, or services, a cookie helps us to recall your registration, membership, or transaction information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your Personal Information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized.

Our Site may also use "Web beacons," also called web bugs, GIFs, or pixel tags to help personalize your experience, similarly to how we use cookies. We may also use Web beacons to gather Non-Personal Information about the number of users who visit our Site, the areas in which they spend their time visiting, and other demographic data. Technology is improving every day and to improve our Services’ operation and function we may introduce new technologies and monitoring techniques without advance notice or consent from you.

**ADDENDUM #3: TYPES OF ADVERTISING**

  * **Contextual Advertising** : We may serve you an advertisement for brakes and shocks based on a used car dealer ad you just viewed or a search you’ve made about used cars on one of our Platforms; this type of relevant advertising based on particular content or search query is called “Contextual Advertising” because it is based on the context of how you used our Platforms. We do not collect any other information about you for Contextual Advertising.
  * **First Party Advertising** : Advertising that is tailored or personalized based on a history of your use of content and participation in features and activities on our Platforms (and may be combined with information from our Facebook Fan page or our other social network sites) over time is based solely on a combination of information that Company or its Operational Service Providers collect from you –  _not from your use of other websites or third parties_. We may share such information anonymously with our Advertisers in order to measure the effectiveness of ads on our Platforms, such as how many users opened or acted on a particular ad.
  * **Network Advertising** : Information about your use of our Platforms combined with similar information about your overall Internet usage across different third party websites or online services used to serve tailored and personalized advertising is generally called “Network Advertising.” Multiple third party websites and online services are involved in this tailored or personalized advertising process, in essence a “network” of advertising providers. Such information about you could include information about your browser, computer, and/or mobile device and general information about your demographics (whether you have provided such information voluntarily or such information is estimated based on your usage history and interests), such as your gender, age, lifestyle, education, home ownership, geographic location, etc. See below for more information about how to identify a Network Advertising ad.

For advertising that is part of a Network Advertising service, you should see a small symbol (also called an icon) attached to a banner ad or other targeted advertising on certain Platforms that can be clicked open for information about why and how you are receiving a particular ad. For more information see [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**ADDENDUM #4:  ** ** ** **Marketing Via Mobile Devices**

Station may provide commercial marketing and advertising opportunities, contests/sweepstakes, and alerts for news, sports, traffic, election coverage, school closings, and weather delivered via mobile devices. You must subscribe to a mobile service or request that we send such information to you via a text message or a wireless voice call (prerecorded or live). Depending on the type of mobile subscription service, you will be asked to submit your name, age or date of birth, mobile telephone number, and/or standard email address. We do not request submission of a wireless email address and if we collect such information inadvertently for a marketing or advertising opportunity, we will attempt to notify you and request a standard email address that does not have a wireless domain name attached to it. You have the right to opt-out of any mobile service in the same manner in which you registered or by notifying us at [privacyadministrator@greatermediadetroit.com](mailto:privacyadminisrator@greatermediadetroit.com) **.**

**ADDENDUM #5:  Email** ** **  
We do not generally keep email correspondence, except for those emails that relate to the on-air programs or operations of our Stations. As required by the Federal Communications Commission (“FCC”), if any part of your email correspondence relates to Station programming or operations, we must place such correspondence in the station’s FCC Public Inspection File, or make the correspondence available via electronic file access at the station to anyone that requests such information. Therefore, be informed that your Personal Information contained in certain emails or text messages will be disclosed to the general public. We request that you not place any Personal Information in your email or text correspondence to Station that pertains to Station programming or operations. You understand and agree that we are not responsible for Personal Information that is improperly disclosed in emails or texts that are made available to the general public in compliance with FCC regulations.

**ADDENDUM #6:  Shopping & E-Commerce**

In connection with the sale of goods and/or services or for contest prize fulfillment, we may request Sensitive Personal Information. “Sensitive Personal Information” includes, but is not limited to, any individual’s: (1) social security number; (2) driver’s license number or state identification card number; (3) employee identification number; or (4) credit or debit card number, with or without any required security code, or PIN. Sensitive Personal Information will only be used for verification of your identity, federal or state tax reporting requirements, and/or to implement and complete the specific activity or event it was submitted for. We will not share your Sensitive Personal Information for marketing or promotional purposes, or with other third parties unless such disclosure is required by law. We may also request additional Personal Information such as full name, billing and shipping address, email address and telephone number and any such information that is required to fulfill your order and to communicate with you regarding your order. We may use your Personal Information (but not your credit card or debit card number) to contact you about future products, services and discounts or to provide such information indirectly from our Advertisers, unless you tell us otherwise (i.e. “opt-out”). We will only use your credit card and debit card number to complete the specific transaction you requested. Alternatively, we may use an independent third party Operational Service Provider to conduct the financial transaction in a secure manner; the third party payment process will be accessible via a hyperlink from the Site or other Services and the Operational Service Provider will be solely responsible for all financial transactions and the collection, use, and storage of your Sensitive Personal Information.

**ADDENDUM #7: Listening Measurement Tracking**

Greater Media websites and mobile applications for Apple and Android all contain the Nielsen SDK.  This technology features Nielsen’s proprietary measurement software, which allows users to contribute to radio listening research, similar to Nielsen’s TV Ratings. You have the right to opt out of allowing the technology to measure your online listening behavior by clicking here [ [http://secure-uat-cert.imrworldwide.com/nielsen_app_optout.html?n=162C4EBA-#](http://secure-uat-cert.imrworldwide.com/nielsen_app_optout.html?n=162C4EBA-)]  While the digital measurement products are not used to identify you in any way, they help Nielsen measure and analyze how consumers engage with media across online, mobile and emerging technologies, and offer insights into consumer behavior.

By clicking on this link <http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy>, you can access more information about the measurement software and learn about your choices with regard to Nielsen’s measurement.

Copyright © 2009-2015, Greater Media, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
